{
    "subject": "resource/Netviewer",
    "predicate": "property/foundation",
    "object": "2001",
    "human_readable": "Netviewer was founded in 2001.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9364088773727417,
            "question": "What events might have influenced the founding of Netviewer in 2001?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8594334125518799,
            "question": "How has technology likely evolved since Netviewer's founding in 2001?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8508720397949219,
            "question": "When was Netviewer founded?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7855287194252014,
            "question": "What are some potential milestones or achievements for Netviewer since its establishment in 2001?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6561912894248962,
            "question": "In what century was Netviewer established?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.636040449142456,
            "question": "How many years ago was Netviewer founded?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5196326375007629,
            "question": "What year did Netviewer begin operations?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4260202646255493,
            "question": "What could you infer about the age of Netviewer based on its founding year?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3214786648750305,
            "question": "Is Netviewer a recent company?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.18921658396720886,
            "question": "If today is 2023, how many years has Netviewer been in existence?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Netviewer was founded in 2001.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6516_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Netviewer a recent company?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6516_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What could you infer about the age of Netviewer based on its founding year?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6516_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year did Netviewer begin operations?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6516_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6516_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6516_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6516_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6516_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6516_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6516_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6516_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6516_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6516_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6516_56.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other triples to evaluate!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe statement \"Netviewer was founded in 2001\" is supported by the information provided in the documents, which consistently state that Netviewer was founded in 2001."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}